mapping ['Work Scheduling Autonomy', 'Decision Making Autonomy', 'Work Methods Autonomy', 'Task Variety', 'Task Significance', 'Task Identity', 'Feedback from Job', 'Job Complexity', 'Information Processing', 'Problem Solving', 'Skill Variety', 'Specialization', 'Social Support', 'Initiated Interdependence ', 'Received Interdependence', 'Interaction Outside Research Group', 'Feedback from Others', 'Faculty/projecdt leader feedback', 'Peer Feedback', 'Ergonomics', 'Physical Demands', 'Work Conditions', 'Equipment Use']
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (nan,nan,'nan',nan);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,1,'What is the primary discipline of your research?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,2,'How many undergraduate students, including yourself, are/were in your research group at the time of your participation?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,3,'How many people in total were in your research group?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,4,'Who was primarily responsible for mentoring and expert advice related to your research?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,5,'What was the primary setting for your research?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,6,'Approximately how was your research time distributed between settings?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,7,'How many hours per week did you work on research-related activities in your most recent research experience?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,8,'During the same time period, how many hours per week did you devote to extracurricular activities (such as clubs, volunteering, sports, music or theater, other hobbies)?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,9,'During the same time period, how many hours per week did you work in a paid job unrelated to your research (on campus or off campus).',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,10,'During the same time period, how many hours per week did you devote to other commitments or obligations that were not listed above? (e.g. caring for family members, unpaid work in a family business).',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (1,11,' During the same time period, what was your status in terms of academic courses or units?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,12,'The research position allows me to make my own decisions about how to schedule my work.',1,'work scheduling autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,13,'The research position allows me to decide on the order in which things are done.',1,'work scheduling autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,14,'The research position allows me to plan how I do my work.',1,'work scheduling autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,15,'The research position gives me a chance to use my personal initiative or judgment in carrying out the work.',1,'decision making autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,16,'The research position allows me to make a lot of decisions on my own.',1,'decision making autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,17,'The research position provides me with significant autonomy in making decisions.',1,'decision making autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,18,'The research position allows me to make decisions about what methods I use to complete my work.',1,'work methods autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,19,'The research position gives me considerable opportunity for independence and freedom in how I do the work.',1,'work methods autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,20,'The research position allows me to decide on my own how to go about doing my work.',1,'work methods autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,21,'The research position involves a great deal of task variety.',1,'task variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,22,'The research position involves doing a number of different things.',1,'task variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,23,'The research position requires the performance of a wide range of tasks.',1,'task variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,24,'The research position involves performing a variety of tasks.',1,'task variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,25,'The results of my work are likely to significantly affect the lives of other people.',1,'task significance');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,26,'The research position itself is very significant and important in the broader scheme of things.',1,'task significance');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,27,'The research position has a large impact on people outside the organization.',1,'task significance');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,28,'The work performed in the research position has a significant impact on people outside my research group.',1,'task significance');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,29,'The research position involves completing a piece of work that has an obvious beginning and end.',1,'task identity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,30,'The research position is arranged so that I can do an entire piece of work from beginning to end.',1,'task identity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,31,'The research position provides me the chance to completely finish the pieces of work I begin.',1,'task identity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,32,'The research position allows me to complete work I start.',1,'task identity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,33,'The work activities themselves provide direct and clear information about the effectiveness (e.g., quality and quantity) of my performance.',1,'feedback from job');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,34,'The research position itself provides feedback on my performance.',1,'feedback from job');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,35,'The research position itself provides me with information about my performance.',1,'feedback from job');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,36,'The research position requires that I only do one task or activity at a time.',1,'job complexity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,37,'The tasks of the research position are simple and uncomplicated.',1,'job complexity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,38,'The research position comprises relatively uncomplicated tasks.',1,'job complexity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,39,'The research position involves performing relatively simple tasks.',1,'job complexity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,40,'The research position requires me to monitor a great deal of information.',1,'information processing');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,41,'The research position requires that I engage in a large amount of thinking.',1,'information processing');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,42,'The research position requires me to keep track of more than one thing at a time.',1,'information processing');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,43,'The research position requires me to analyze a lot of information.',1,'information processing');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,44,'The research position involves solving problems that have no obvious correct answer.',1,'problem solving');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,45,'The research position requires me to be creative.',1,'problem solving');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,46,'The research position often involves dealing with problems that I have not met before.',1,'problem solving');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,47,'The research position requires unique ideas or solutions to problems.',1,'problem solving');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,48,'The research position requires a variety of skills.',1,'skill variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,49,'The research position requires me to utilize a variety of different skills in order to complete the work.',1,'skill variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,50,'The research position requires me to use a number of complex or high-level skills.',1,'skill variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,51,'The research position requires the use of a number of skills.',1,'skill variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,52,'The research position is highly specialized in terms of purpose, tasks, or activities.',1,'specialization');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,53,'The tools, procedures, materials, and so forth used in this research position are highly specialized in terms of purpose.',1,'specialization');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,54,'The research position requires very specialized knowledge and skills.',1,'specialization');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,55,'The research position requires a depth of knowledge and expertise.',1,'specialization');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,56,'I have the opportunity to develop close friendships in this research position.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,57,'I have the chance in this research position to get to know other people.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,58,'I have the opportunity to meet with others in this research position.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,59,'My group leader is concerned about the welfare of the people in the research group.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,60,'People I work with take a personal interest in me.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,61,'People I work with are friendly.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,62,'The research position requires me to accomplish my work before others complete their work.',1,'initiated interdependence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,63,'Other jobs depend directly on my job.',1,'initiated interdepenence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,64,'Unless my job gets done, other jobs cannot be completed.',1,'initiated interdependence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,65,'My research activities are greatly affected by the work of other people.',1,'received interdependence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,66,'The research project depends on the work of many different people for its completion.',1,'received interdependence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,67,'My work cannot be done unless others do their work.',1,'received interdependence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,68,'The research position requires spending a great deal of time with people outside my research group.',1,'interaction outside research group');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,69,'The research position involves interaction with people who are not members of my research group.',1,'interaction outside research group');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,70,'In this research position, I frequently communicate with people who do not work in the same research group as I do.',1,'interaction outside research group');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,71,'The research position involves a great deal of interaction with people outside my research group.',1,'interaction outside research group');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,72,'I receive a great deal of information from my project leader and peers about my work performance.',1,'feedback from others');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,73,'Other people in the research group, such as group leader and peers, provide information about the effectiveness (e.g., quality and quantity) of my work performance.',1,'feedback from others');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,74,'I receive feedback on my performance from other people in my group (such as my project leader or peers).',1,'feedback from others');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,75,'I receive a great deal of information from my group leader about my work performance.',1,'faculty/project leader feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,76,'My group leader provides information about the effectiveness (e.g., quality and quantity) of my work performance.',1,'faculty/projecdt leader feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,77,'I receive feedback on my performance from my group leader.',1,'faculty/project leader feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,78,'I receive a great deal of information from other students in my group about my work performance.',1,'peer feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,79,'Other students in the research group provide information about the effectiveness (e.g., quality and quantity) of my work performance.',1,'peer feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,80,'I receive feedback on my performance from other students in my group.',1,'peer feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,81,'The seating arrangements in my research space are adequate (e.g., ample opportunities to sit, comfortable chairs, good postural support).',1,'ergonomics');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,82,'The research space allows for all size differences between people in terms of clearance, reach, eye height, legroom, etc.',1,'ergonomics');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,83,'The research position involves excessive reaching.',1,'ergonomics');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,84,'The research position requires a great deal of muscular endurance.',1,'physical demands');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,85,'The research position requires a great deal of muscular strength.',1,'physical demands');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,86,'The research position requires a lot of physical effort.',1,'physical demands');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,87,'The research space is free from excessive noise.',1,'work conditions');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,88,'The climate in the research space is comfortable in terms of temperature and humidity.',1,'work conditions');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,89,'The research position has a low risk of accident.',1,'work conditions');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,90,'The research position takes place in an environment free from health hazards (e.g., chemicals, fumes, etc.).',1,'work conditions');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,91,'The research position occurs in a clean environment.',1,'work conditions');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,92,'The research position involves the use of a variety of different equipment.',1,'equipment use');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,93,'The research position involves the use of complex equipment or technology.',1,'equipment use');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (1,94,'A lot of time was required to learn the equipment used in the research position.',1,'equipment use');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (2,1,'What type of organization do you work in?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (2,2,'Which of degrees did you earn and what year did you earn them in (fill all that apply)',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (2,3,'In which year did you work at the position for which you are answering the survey?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (2,4,'How do you spend your time in this job (fieldwork)?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (2,5,'How do you spend your time in this job (lab work)?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type) VALUES (2,6,'How do you spend your time in this job (computer work)?',0);
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,7,'The job allows me to make my own decisions about how to schedule my work.',1,'work scheduling autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,8,'The job allows me to decide on the order in which things are done.',1,'work scheduling autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,9,'The job allows me to plan how I do my work.',1,'work scheduling autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,10,'The job gives me a chance to use my personal initiative or judgment in carrying out the work.',1,'decision making autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,11,'The job allows me to make a lot of decisions on my own.',1,'decision making autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,12,'The job provides me with significant autonomy in making decisions.',1,'decision making autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,13,'The job allows me to make decisions about what methods I use to complete my work.',1,'work methods autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,14,'The job gives me considerable opportunity for independence and freedom in how I do the work.',1,'work methods autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,15,'The job allows me to decide on my own how to go about doing my work.',1,'work methods autonomy');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,16,'The job involves a great deal of task variety.',1,'task variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,17,'The job involves doing a number of different things.',1,'task variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,18,'The job requires the performance of a wide range of tasks.',1,'task variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,19,'The job involves performing a variety of tasks.',1,'task variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,20,'The results of my work are likely to significantly affect the lives of other people.',1,'task significance');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,21,'The job itself is very significant and important in the broader scheme of things.',1,'task significance');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,22,'The job has a large impact on people outside the organization.',1,'task significance');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,23,'The work performed in the job has a significant impact on people outside my research group.',1,'task significance');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,24,'The job involves completing a piece of work that has an obvious beginning and end.',1,'task identity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,25,'The job is arranged so that I can do an entire piece of work from beginning to end.',1,'task identity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,26,'The job provides me the chance to completely finish the pieces of work I begin.',1,'task identity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,27,'The job allows me to complete work I start.',1,'task identity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,28,'The work activities themselves provide direct and clear information about the effectiveness (e.g., quality and quantity) of my performance.',1,'feedback from job');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,29,'The job itself provides feedback on my performance.',1,'feedback from job');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,30,'The job itself provides me with information about my performance.',1,'feedback from job');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,31,'The job requires that I only do one task or activity at a time.',1,'job complexity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,32,'The tasks of the job are simple and uncomplicated.',1,'job complexity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,33,'The job comprises relatively uncomplicated tasks.',1,'job complexity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,34,'The job involves performing relatively simple tasks.',1,'job complexity');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,35,'The job requires me to monitor a great deal of information.',1,'information processing');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,36,'The job requires that I engage in a large amount of thinking.',1,'information processing');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,37,'The job requires me to keep track of more than one thing at a time.',1,'information processing');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,38,'The job requires me to analyze a lot of information.',1,'information processing');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,39,'The job involves solving problems that have no obvious correct answer.',1,'problem solving');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,40,'The job requires me to be creative.',1,'problem solving');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,41,'The job often involves dealing with problems that I have not met before.',1,'problem solving');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,42,'The job requires unique ideas or solutions to problems.',1,'problem solving');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,43,'The job requires a variety of skills.',1,'skill variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,44,'The job requires me to utilize a variety of different skills in order to complete the work.',1,'skill variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,45,'The job requires me to use a number of complex or high-level skills.',1,'skill variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,46,'The job requires the use of a number of skills.',1,'skill variety');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,47,'The job is highly specialized in terms of purpose, tasks, or activities.',1,'specialization');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,48,'The tools, procedures, materials, and so forth used in this job are highly specialized in terms of purpose.',1,'specialization');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,49,'The job requires very specialized knowledge and skills.',1,'specialization');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,50,'The job requires a depth of knowledge and expertise.',1,'specialization');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,51,'I have the opportunity to develop close friendships in this job.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,52,'I have the chance in this job to get to know other people.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,53,'I have the opportunity to meet with others in this job.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,54,'My group leader is concerned about the welfare of the people in the research group.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,55,'People I work with take a personal interest in me.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,56,'People I work with are friendly.',1,'social support');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,57,'The job requires me to accomplish my work before others complete their work.',1,'initiated interdependence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,58,'Other jobs depend directly on my job.',1,'initiated interdepenence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,59,'Unless my job gets done, other jobs cannot be completed.',1,'initiated interdependence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,60,'My research activities are greatly affected by the work of other people.',1,'received interdependence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,61,'The research project depends on the work of many different people for its completion.',1,'received interdependence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,62,'My work cannot be done unless others do their work.',1,'received interdependence');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,63,'The job requires spending a great deal of time with people outside my research group.',1,'interaction outside research group');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,64,'The job involves interaction with people who are not members of my research group.',1,'interaction outside research group');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,65,'In this job, I frequently communicate with people who do not work in the same research group as I do.',1,'interaction outside research group');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,66,'The job involves a great deal of interaction with people outside my research group.',1,'interaction outside research group');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,67,'I receive a great deal of information from my project leader and peers about my work performance.',1,'feedback from others');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,68,'Other people in the research group, such as group leader and peers, provide information about the effectiveness (e.g., quality and quantity) of my work performance.',1,'feedback from others');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,69,'I receive feedback on my performance from other people in my group (such as my project leader or peers).',1,'feedback from others');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,70,'I receive a great deal of information from my group leader about my work performance.',1,'faculty/project leader feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,71,'My group leader provides information about the effectiveness (e.g., quality and quantity) of my work performance.',1,'faculty/projecdt leader feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,72,'I receive feedback on my performance from my group leader.',1,'faculty/project leader feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,73,'I receive a great deal of information from other students in my group about my work performance.',1,'peer feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,74,'Other students in the research group provide information about the effectiveness (e.g., quality and quantity) of my work performance.',1,'peer feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,75,'I receive feedback on my performance from other students in my group.',1,'peer feedback');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,76,'The seating arrangements in my research space are adequate (e.g., ample opportunities to sit, comfortable chairs, good postural support).',1,'ergonomics');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,77,'The research space allows for all size differences between people in terms of clearance, reach, eye height, legroom, etc.',1,'ergonomics');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,78,'The job involves excessive reaching.',1,'ergonomics');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,79,'The job requires a great deal of muscular endurance.',1,'physical demands');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,80,'The job requires a great deal of muscular strength.',1,'physical demands');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,81,'The job requires a lot of physical effort.',1,'physical demands');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,82,'The research space is free from excessive noise.',1,'work conditions');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,83,'The climate in the research space is comfortable in terms of temperature and humidity.',1,'work conditions');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,84,'The job has a low risk of accident.',1,'work conditions');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,85,'The job takes place in an environment free from health hazards (e.g., chemicals, fumes, etc.).',1,'work conditions');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,86,'The job occurs in a clean environment.',1,'work conditions');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,87,'The job involves the use of a variety of different equipment.',1,'equipment use');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,88,'The job involves the use of complex equipment or technology.',1,'equipment use');
INSERT INTO MultipleChoiceQuestions (SurveyID, Position, Prompt, Type, Characteristic) VALUES (2,89,'A lot of time was required to learn the equipment used in the job.',1,'equipment use');
